Guide to the Yale University Corporation Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Corporation records
1714-2007
RU 164
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
98.52
The records consist of subject files, correspondence, minutes of meetings, memoranda, proposals, and working papers related to the Yale University Corporation's policy, planning, and administrative functions. Also included are early records concerning the Church of Christ at Yale, circa1756-1899.
Yale Corporation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 1-A (YRG 1-A), Minutes of meetings and administrative records of the Yale Corporation.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Biographical / Historical
Yale's charter provides that its governing body, known legally as "the President and Fellows of Yale College"--or more commonly, as "the Corporation"--shall have the government, care and management of the College... and make such reasonable laws... as they think fit and proper for the instruction and education of the students." The Corporation is the final authority in the governance of the University. Although it is not involved in most of the day-to-day details of University operation, the Corporation must approve all major changes in educational, institutional, or financial policy. The officers of the University are appointed by the Corporation. The Corporation is made up of 19 individuals called Fellows. There are three members ex-officii: the President of the University, and the Governor and Lt. Governor of Connecticut; ten "Successors to the Original Trustees," who elect their own successors; and six alumni Fellows, elected by and from the Yale alumni body.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files, correspondence, minutes of meetings, memoranda, proposals, and working papers related to the Yale University Corporation's policy, planning, and administrative functions. Also included are early records concerning the Church of Christ at Yale, circa1756-1899.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Religion; Yale College (1718-1887). Church of Christ; Yale Corporation
- Agendas and memoranda, 1952-1984; Accession 19ND-A-423; 1; (2 boxes) (Box 1–2)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2035.
- Yale Corporation charts prepared by David Alan Richards, 1969; Accession 19ND-A-496
  The materials are open for research.
  - Yale Corporation family tree (Box 1)
- Meeting minutes (carbon copies) and Hillhouse-Stokes letterbook, 1904-1962; Accession 1965-A-002
  - Yale Corporation Minutes (carbon), 1904-1962
    - 1904 Feb 24 -1911 Sep 18 (Box 1)
    - 1911 Oct 16 -1915 Apr 15 (Box 1)
    - 1915 May 17 -1919 Jan 20 (Box 2)
    - 1919 Feb 17 -1922 Oct 14 (Box 2)
    - 1922 Nov 18 -1926 Jan 9 (Box 3)
    - 1926 Feb 13 -1929 Jun 17 (Box 3)
    - 1929 Oct 12 -1934 Feb 3 (Box 4)
    - 1934 Apr 14 -1939 Feb 11 (Box 4)
    - 1939 Apr 15 -1943 Oct 9 (Box 5)
    - 1943 Nov 13 -1947 Jun 16 (Box 6)
    - 1947 Oct 11 -1952 Apr 19 (Box 7)
    - 1952 May 10 - 1952 Jun 5 (Box 8)
    - 1954 Sep -1957 Oct (Box 9)
    - 1957 Nov -1960 Apr (Box 10)
    - 1960 Apr -1961 Oct (Box 11)
    - 1961 Nov -1962 Nov (Box 12)
  - Stokes-Hillhouse letter notebook (carbon), 1905-1912 (Box 20)
- Yale Corporation records, 1921-1972; Accession 1973-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - SUBJECT FILE, Series I
    - Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda
      - Admissions and student appointments, 1922-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
      - Air Science, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
      - Alumni Board, 1922-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 7)
      - Alumni Fellows, 1922-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Alumni Fellows, 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Alumni Fund, 1922-1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - American Council on Education, 1922 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - American Philosophical Association, 1931 March 20-April 20 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - American University in Europe, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Anatomy, 1933 October 29-November 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Anthropoid Experiment Station, 1930 April 12-1931 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Anthropology, 1937-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16 - 19)
      - Architecture, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20 - 21)
      - Area Studies, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Area Studies: recommendations, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Art, 1921-1938 (Box 2, Folder 24 - 34)
      - Art, 1938-1950 (Box 3, Folder 35 - 41)
      - Art and Architecture recommendations
        - A-K, 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
        - L-P, 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 43)
        - R-Z, 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Art Gallery, 1940-1958 (Box 4, Folder 45 - 51)
      - Arts and Sciences, 1924 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Astronomy, 1933-1959 (Box 4, Folder 53 - 56)
      - Athletic Association, 1922-1956 (Box 5, Folder 57 - 58)
      - Audio Visual Center, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Babylonian Collection, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Biochemistry, 1953-1958 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Biophysics, 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 65 - 66)
      - Bishop Museum, 1925-1948 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Botany, 1922-1958 (Box 5, Folder 68 - 70)
      - Budgets, 1922-1955 (Box 6, Folder 71 - 72)
      - Buildings, 1923-1935 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Bureau of Appointments, 1921-1929 (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - By-laws, 1923] 1937-1957 (Box 6, Folder 75 - 76)
      - Cabinet, The, 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Calendar, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Carnegie Teaching Fellows, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 81 - 82)
      - Celtic Literature, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Chapel, 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Chemical Engineering, 1929-1937 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - Chemical Engineering, 1938-1959 (Box 7, Folder 86 - 87)
      - Chemistry, 1921-1945 (Box 7, Folder 88 - 91)
      - Chemistry, 1945-1959 (Box 8, Folder 92 - 95)
      - Civil Engineering, 1922-1940 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - Civil Engineering, 1941-1959 (Box 9, Folder 97 - 98)
      - Classics, 1921-1949 (Box 9, Folder 99 - 100)
      - Classics, 1949-1959 (Box 10, Folder 101 - 102)
      - Colgate professorship, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Cosmopolitan Club, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Correspondence with Corporation members, 1923-1969 (Box 10, Folder 106 - 108)
      - Degrees, 1921-1958 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Departmental Chairmen, 1921-1958 (Box 11, Folder 110)
      - Design, 1950-1958 (Box 11, Folder 111)
      - Dining halls, 1939-1945 (Box 11, Folder 112)
      - Divinity School, 1922-1935 (Box 11, Folder 113 - 115)
      - Divinity School, 1936-1958 (Box 12, Folder 116 - 120)
      - Drama, 1922-1935 (Box 12, Folder 121)
      - Drama, 1936-1958 (Box 13, Folder 122 - 124)
      - Economics, 1923-1945 (Box 13, Folder 125 - 126)
      - Economics, 1945-1959 (Box 14, Folder 127 - 129)
      - Education, 1921-1959 (Box 15, Folder 130 - 133)
      - Electrical Engineering, 1921-1937 (Box 15, Folder 134 - 135)
      - Electrical Engineering, 1938-1958 (Box 16, Folder 136 - 137)
      - Engineering, School of, 1932-1954 (Box 16, Folder 138 - 139)
      - Engineering and Applied Science: recommendations, 1940-1959 (Box 16, Folder 140)
      - Engineering Drawing, 1923-1942 (Box 16, Folder 141)
      - Engineering Mechanics, 1922-1939 (Box 16, Folder 142)
      - English
        - 1921-1926 (Box 17, Folder 143)
        - 1927-1932 (Box 17, Folder 144)
        - 1932-1937 (Box 17, Folder 145)
        - 1937-1943 (Box 17, Folder 146)
        - 1943-1947 (Box 18, Folder 147)
        - 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 148)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 149)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 150)
        - Recommendations, 1953-1959 (Box 19, Folder 151)
      - Faculty, 1931-1960 (Box 19, Folder 152)
      - Faculty Club, 1925-1931 (Box 19, Folder 153)
      - Faculty vitae: A-Z, 1969 September 10, undated (Box 19, Folder 154 - 156)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1922-1934 (Box 19, Folder 157)
      - Foreign Area Studies, 1943-1946 (Box 20, Folder 158)
      - Foreign Area Studies, 1951-1955 (Box 20, Folder 159)
      - Forestry School
        - 1921-1937 (Box 20, Folder 160)
        - 1937-1945 (Box 20, Folder 161)
        - 1945-1956 (Box 20, Folder 162)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 164)
      - French
        - 1926-1937 (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - 1937-1945 (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - 1947-1949 (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - 1947-1955 (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 169)
      - Freshman Year
        - 1922-1941 (Box 22, Folder 170)
        - 1942-1954 (Box 22, Folder 171)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 172)
      - Freshman Year: recommendations, 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Geochronometric Laboratory, 1951-1956 (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Geochronometric Laboratory, 1953-1958 (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Geography, 1949-1959 (Box 22, Folder 176 - 177)
      - Geology
        - 1923-1937 (Box 22, Folder 178)
        - 1937-1952 (Box 23, Folder 179)
        - 1952-1959 (Box 23, Folder 180)
      - Geology: recommendations, 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 181)
      - German, 1921-1959 (Box 23, Folder 182 - 184)
      - Germanic Languages: recommendations, 1953-1959 (Box 23, Folder 185)
      - Gift acknowledgments, 1929-1952 (Box 24, Folder 186)
      - Gifts to Yale, 1920-1958 (Box 24, Folder 187)
      - Government and International Relations, 1933-1945 (Box 24, Folder 188)
      - Graduate School, 1921-1935 (Box 24, Folder 189 - 192)
      - Graduate School, 1935-1958 (Box 25, Folder 193 - 197)
      - Gymnasium, 1922-1933 (Box 25, Folder 200)
      - Health, 1921-22 (Box 26, Folder 201)
      - History, 1922-25 (Box 26, Folder 202 - 207)
      - History, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 208 - 209)
      - History of Art, 1940-1959 (Box 27, Folder 210 - 212)
      - History, the Arts and Letters, 1932-1935 (Box 27, Folder 213)
      - Honorary degrees, 1922-1957 (Box 27, Folder 214 - 215)
      - Human Relations Area Files, 1953-1959 (Box 27, Folder 216 - 217)
      - Human Resources, study of, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 218)
      - Indic and Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1947-1959 (Box 28, Folder 219 - 220)
      - Industrial Administration, 1932, 1950-1959 (Box 28, Folder 221 - 222)
      - Industrial Engineering, 1925-1932 (Box 28, Folder 223)
      - Infirmary, 1928-29 (Box 28, Folder 224)
      - Institute of Far Eastern Languages, 1945-1959 (Box 28, Folder 225 - 228)
      - Institute of Human Relations, 1929-1959 (Box 29, Folder 229 - 233)
      - Institute of International Studies, 1942-1951 (Box 29, Folder 234)
      - International cable registrations, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 235)
      - Labor and Management Center, 1945-1954 (Box 30, Folder 236)
      - Laboratories, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 237)
      - Law School
        - 1921-1937 (Box 30, Folder 238 - 241)
        - 1937-1952 (Box 31, Folder 242 - 246)
        - 1952-1959 (Box 32, Folder 247 - 250)
      - Library
        - 1921-1930 (Box 32, Folder 251 - 252)
        - 1931-1942 (Box 33, Folder 253 - 256)
        - 1942-1959 (Box 34, Folder 257 - 260)
      - Machine Tool exhibition, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 261)
      - Marsh Botanical Garden, 1922-1927 (Box 35, Folder 262)
      - Mathematics, 1922-1959 (Box 35, Folder 263 - 268)
      - Mechanical Engineering, 1921-1959 (Box 36, Folder 269 - 272)
      - Medical Library, 1939-1944 (Box 36, Folder 273)
      - Medical School
        - 1921-25 (Box 36, Folder 274 - 275)
        - 1925-1935 (Box 37, Folder 276 - 281)
        - 1935-1940 (Box 38, Folder 282 - 285)
        - 1940-1944 (Box 39, Folder 286 - 288)
        - 1944-1947 (Box 40, Folder 289 - 291)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 41, Folder 292 - 298)
        - 1950-1952 Jun (Box 42, Folder 299 - 306)
        - 1952 Dec-1954 (Box 43, Folder 307 - 311)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 44, Folder 312 - 315)
        - 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 316 - 321)
        - No date (Box 46, Folder 322 - 323)
      - Meetings: memoranda and correspondence re: date change, 1958, 1928-1938 (Box 46, Folder 324)
      - Microbiology, 1950-1956 (Box 47, Folder 325 - 326)
      - Military Intelligence Service Language School, 1943-1945 (Box 47, Folder 327)
      - Military Science: recommendations for military appointment, 1923-1959 (Box 47, Folder 328)
      - Mining and Metallurgy, 1922-1942 (Box 47, Folder 329 - 330)
      - Modern Language Association, 1922-23 (Box 47, Folder 331)
      - Motor vehicle traffic: conference on, 1923-24 (Box 47, Folder 332)
      - Music School, 1922-1945 (Box 47, Folder 333 - 334)
      - Music School, 1945-1959 (Box 48, Folder 335 - 337)
      - National Academy of Sciences, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 338)
      - National Tuberculosis Association, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 339)
      - Natural Preserve, 1925-27 (Box 48, Folder 340)
      - Naval Science, 1926-1955 (Box 48, Folder 341 - 342)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1947-1959 (Box 48, Folder 343)
      - New England Association of Collegiate Registrars, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 344)
      - New England Federation of Harvard Clubs, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 345)
      - New Haven Association of Kindergartens, 1923-24 (Box 48, Folder 346)
      - New Haven Hospital, 1922-1953 (Box 48, Folder 347 - 349)
      - New Haven Police Department, 1925 (Box 49, Folder 350)
      - New Haven Progress Exposition, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 351)
      - Nursing School, 1923-1948 (Box 49, Folder 352 - 356)
      - Nursing School, 1948-1959 (Box 50, Folder 357 - 360)
      - Nutrition, Laboratory of, 1943-1944 (Box 50, Folder 361)
      - Nutrition, Institute of, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 362)
      - Observatory, 1921-1935 (Box 50, Folder 363)
      - Oriental Studies, 1936-1946 (Box 50, Folder 364)
      - Peabody Museum, 1921-1959 (Box 51, Folder 365 - 370)
      - Personnel department, 1927-1937 (Box 51, Folder 371)
      - Personnel register, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 372)
      - Personnel study, 1937-1942 (Box 51, Folder 373)
      - Philosophy, 1921-1959 (Box 52, Folder 374 - 378)
      - Physics
        - 1921-1937 (Box 52, Folder 379 - 380)
        - 1937-1955 (Box 53, Folder 381 - 384)
        - 1955-1959 (Box 54, Folder 385 - 387)
      - Physiological Chemistry, 1922-1935 (Box 54, Folder 388)
      - Physiological Sciences, 1925-1946 (Box 54, Folder 389)
      - Physiology, 1922-1959 (Box 54, Folder 390 - 392)
      - Physiology, 1950-1959 (Box 55, Folder 393)
      - Plant Science, 1949-1956 (Box 55, Folder 394 - 396)
      - Political Science, 1921-1959 (Box 55, Folder 397 - 399)
      - President James R. Angell, 1921-1928 (Box 55, Folder 400)
      - President James R. Angell, 1922-1937 (Box 56, Folder 401 - 403)
      - President Charles Seymour, 1937-1951 (Box 56, Folder 404 - 405)
      - President Charles Seymour, 1947-1950 (Box 57, Folder 406)
      - President A. Whitney Griswold, 1950-1970 (Box 57, Folder 407)
      - Primate Biology, 1935-1955 (Box 57, Folder 408 - 411)
      - Primate Biology, 1955-1956 (Box 58, Folder 412)
      - Provost, 1921-1959 (Box 58, Folder 413 - 415)
      - Psychology, 1928-1945 (Box 58, Folder 416 - 417)
      - Psychology, 1952-1959 (Box 59, Folder 418 - 421)
      - Psychology Clinic, 1925-1931 (Box 59, Folder 422)
      - Psychology, Institute of, 1924-25 (Box 59, Folder 423)
      - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1921 (Box 59, Folder 424)
      - Race relations, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 425)
      - Religion, 1923-27 (Box 59, Folder 426 - 428)
      - Requisitions: office supplies and services, 1966-68 (Box 60, Folder 429 - 430)
      - Retirement and resignations, 1921-61 (Box 60, Folder 431)
      - Romance Languages, 1921-1959 (Box 60, Folder 432 - 434)
      - Salaries, 1929, 1958-1959 (Box 60, Folder 435)
      - Secretary's office: Holden, R.A., 1953-1957 (Box 61, Folder 436)
      - Secretary's office: Hutchins, R.M., 1921-1925 (Box 61, Folder 437)
      - Secretary's office: Lohmann, Carl C., 1926-1950 (Box 61, Folder 438 - 443)
      - Office of Selective Service, 1945-1950 (Box 62, Folder 444)
      - Semitics, 1922-1935 (Box 62, Folder 445)
      - Sheffield Scientific School, 1921-1924 (Box 62, Folder 446 - 447)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1947-1959 (Box 62, Folder 448 - 449)
      - Social and Political Sciences, 1922-1937 (Box 62, Folder 450 - 451)
      - Sociology, 1937-1953 (Box 63, Folder 452 - 454)
      - Southeast Asian Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 63, Folder 455 - 456)
      - Spanish, 1929-1937 (Box 63, Folder 457)
      - Spanish and Italian, 1923-1952 (Box 63, Folder 458 - 460)
      - Statistics: Yale College and Sheffield Scientific School, 1923 (Box 64, Folder 461 - 463)
      - Student Appointment Bureau, 1943-1955 (Box 64, Folder 464 - 465)
      - Summer Language, 1956-1958 (Box 64, Folder 466)
      - Summer session, 1946-1949 (Box 64, Folder 467)
      - Office of Teaching Training, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 468)
      - Master of Arts in Teaching program, 1954-1958 (Box 64, Folder 469 - 470)
      - Technology project, 1954-1959 (Box 64, Folder 471)
      - Time magazine, 1923 (Box 64, Folder 472)
      - Transportation, 1925-1959 (Box 64, Folder 473 - 475)
      - Transportation: Bureau of Highway Traffic, 1953-1959 (Box 65, Folder 476)
      - Treasurer's Office
        - 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 477 - 481)
        - 1925-1930 (Box 66, Folder 482 - 488)
        - 1929-1934 (Box 67, Folder 489 - 493)
        - 1934-1938 (Box 68, Folder 494 - 497)
        - 1938-1941 (Box 69, Folder 498 - 500)
        - 1941-1947 (Box 70, Folder 501 - 506)
        - 1947-1954 (Box 71, Folder 507 - 513)
        - 1954-1958 (Box 72, Folder 514 - 518)
        - 1957-1960 (Box 73, Folder 519 - 520)
      - Trustees, original: successors of, 1925-1947 (Box 73, Folder 521)
      - Tutoring schools: recommendations, undated (Box 73, Folder 522)
      - Union: demands for new contract, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 523)
      - Unitarian Laymen's League, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 524)
      - University Council, 1922-1957 (Box 74, Folder 525 - 526)
      - University Development, Division of, 1946-1950 (Box 74, Folder 527)
      - University Development, President's Committee on, 1939-1941 (Box 74, Folder 528)
      - University Health, 1933-1952 (Box 74, Folder 529 - 530)
      - University Health, 1954-1958 (Box 75, Folder 531 - 533)
      - University Press, 1923-1967 (Box 75, Folder 534 - 535)
      - Visiting lecturers, 1921-1923 (Box 75, Folder 536)
      - Yale College, 1921-1959 (Box 75, Folder 537 - 541)
      - Yale College: residential colleges, 1930-1933 (Box 75, Folder 542)
      - Yale College: residential colleges, 1933-1959 (Box 76, Folder 543 - 546)
      - Young Men's Christian Association, 1925 (Box 76, Folder 547)
      - Zoology, 1921-1928 (Box 76, Folder 548)
      - Zoology, 1928-1959 (Box 77, Folder 549 - 554)
  - COMMITTEE MEETINGS: PROPOSALS AND CORRESPONDENCE, Series II
    - Alumni relations, 1939-1941 (Box 78, Folder 555)
    - Architectural plan, 1921-1956 (Box 78, Folder 556 - 561)
    - Buildings and grounds, 1927-1957 (Box 78, Folder 562)
    - Educational policy, 1921-1957 (Box 78, Folder 563 - 564)
    - Finance, 1938-1946 (Box 78, Folder 565)
    - Freshman deanship, 1936-1941 (Box 78, Folder 566)
    - Library and museums, 1938-1946 (Box 78, Folder 567)
    - Patents, 1937-1958 (Box 79, Folder 568)
    - Personnel problems: retirement allowance plan, 1940 (Box 79, Folder 569)
    - Portfolio: control of the M.N. Buckner's committee, 1937 (Box 79, Folder 570)
    - President: selection of a, 1935-1940 (Box 79, Folder 571)
    - Scientific research, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 572)
    - Silliman lectures, 1927 (Box 79, Folder 573)
    - Survey of the Presidency, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 574)
    - Undergraduate classes: limitation of size, 1938 (Box 79, Folder 575)
    - War memorials: World War II, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 576)
  - MEETINGS: MINUTES, PROPOSALS, AGENDA and WORKING PAPERS, Series III
    - 1958 Oct-Dec (Box 80, Folder 577 - 579)
    - 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 80, Folder 580 - 584)
    - 1959 Oct-Dec (Box 81, Folder 585 - 590)
    - 1960 Jan-Apr (Box 81, Folder 591 - 596)
    - 1960 May-Dec (Box 82, Folder 597 - 606)
    - 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 83, Folder 607 - 616)
    - 1961 Oct-Dec (Box 84, Folder 617 - 622)
    - 1962 Jan-Apr (Box 84, Folder 623 - 628)
    - 1962 May-Dec (Box 85, Folder 629 - 638)
    - 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 86, Folder 639 - 648)
    - 1963 Oct-Dec (Box 87, Folder 649 - 654)
    - 1964 Feb-Apr (Box 87, Folder 655 - 660)
    - 1964 May-Dec (Box 88, Folder 661 - 670)
    - 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 89, Folder 671 - 680)
    - 1965 Oct-Dec (Box 90, Folder 681 - 687)
    - 1966 Jan-Mar (Box 90, Folder 688 - 692)
    - 1966 Mar-Jun (Box 91, Folder 693 - 701)
    - 1966 Jun-Oct (Box 92, Folder 702 - 707)
    - 1966 Nov-Dec (Box 93, Folder 708 - 712)
    - 1967 Jan (Box 93, Folder 713 - 714)
    - 1967 Mar-May (Box 94, Folder 715 - 720)
    - 1967 Jun (Box 95, Folder 721 - 724)
    - 1967 Oct-Nov (Box 96, Folder 725 - 730)
    - 1967 Dec (Box 97, Folder 731 - 732)
    - 1968 Jan-Apr (Box 97, Folder 733 - 738)
    - 1968 May-Jun (Box 98, Folder 739 - 743)
    - 1968 Oct-Dec (Box 99, Folder 744 - 748)
    - 1969 Feb-May (Box 100, Folder 749 - 753)
    - 1969 Jun-Oct (Box 101, Folder 754 - 758)
    - 1969 Oct-Dec (Box 102, Folder 759 - 763)
    - 1970 Jan-May (Box 103, Folder 764 - 767)
    - 1970 Jun-Sep (Box 104, Folder 768 - 773)
    - 1970 Oct (Box 105, Folder 774 - 777)
    - 1971 Oct (Box 105, Folder 778)
    - 1971 Oct-Dec (Box 106, Folder 779 - 782)
    - 1972 Jan-May (Box 107, Folder 783 - 787)
    - 1972 May-Jun (Box 108, Folder 788 - 790)
    - Records: excerpts, 1937-1955 (Box 109, Folder 791)
    - Resolutions, 1927-1958 (Box 109, Folder 792 - 794)
- Request for use of church for commencement, 1815; Accession 1979-A-016
  - Request for use of church for commencement, 1815 (Box 1)
- Correspondence and reports, 1795-1838; Accession 1979-A-017
  - Correspondence and reports, 1795-1838 (Box 1)
- Meeting minutes and subject files, 1975-1979, 1984; Accession 1991-A-027
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2034
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by topic, thereunder chronologically.
  - Corporation Meetings
    - 1975 Feb 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1975 Mar 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1975 Apr 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1975 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1975 Sep 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1975 Oct 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1975 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1975 Dec 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1976 Feb 7 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1976 Mar 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1976 Apr 10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1976 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1976 Jun 11 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1976 Sep 25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1976 Nov 20 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1976 Dec 16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1977 Jan 22 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1977 Mar 5 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1977 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1977 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1977 Jun 10 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1977 Aug 2 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1977 Oct 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1977 Nov 19 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1977 Dec 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1978 Jan 21 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1978 Jan 3 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Corporation Meetings
    - 1978 Sep 22-23 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1978 Apr 15 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1978 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 1978 Jun 9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Special Meetings
    - 1978 Jun 16 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 1978 Dec 16 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 1978 Nov 4 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Institutional Policies, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)